The Audience Isn't The Only One Watching.
The Task is a horror film directed by Alex Orwell.
Something diabolical is taking place on the set of "The Task" a new reality show in which players complete
terrifying missions within the confines of an abandoned prison hoping to win a hefty cash prize.
As six young students explore their new environment, malicious spirits make their presence known in the most gruesome ways imaginable, Unable to
escape the labyrinthine prison, the contestants become unwitting pawns caught at the centre of a blood-soaked night of terror.
Connie, played by Alexandra Staden.
Big Daddy, played by Victor McGuire.
Taylor, played by Adam Rayner.
Angel, played by Antonia Campbell-Hughes.
Shoe, played by Ashley Mulheron.
Randall, played by Marc Pickering.
The Task is a 2011 British horror film directed by Alex Orwell, written by  Kenny Yakkel, produced by
Christopher Milburn and Courtney Solomon, and starring Alexandra Staden, Victor McGuire and Adam Rayner.
The film, inspired by MTV's Fear, was produced by After Dark Originals and
released by Lions Gate Entertainment on 28 January 2011.
The tone is dark.